RG 079:001, Department of Environmental Protection: Central Office
Connecticut State Library
- Series 7. Bureau of Administration, 1967-1981; 1988-024 (part)
  - Assistant Commissioner Ralph Adkins Subject Files, 1967-1981
    - Geological and Natural History Survey-Source Material (Box 9-3)
    - George Dudley Seymour Fund (Box 9-3)
    - Giant’s Neck-East Lyme (Box 9-3)
    - Gorski Reports (Box 9-3)
    - Goodwin Forest Conservation Center (Box 9-3)
    - Governor’s budget Hearing, 1974 (Box 9-3)
    - Governor Meskill’s Office Correspondence (Box 9-3)
    - Gypsy Moth Control Program (Box 9-3)
    - Governor-Environmental Statements (Box 9-3)
    - Governor’s Task Force-Agriculture (Box 9-3)
    - Governor’s Task Force for DEP (Box 9-3)
    - Grant Approvals (Box 9-3)
    - Harkness Memorial State Park (Box 9-3)
    - Hartford National Bank (Box 9-3)
    - Health Department (Box 9-3)
    - Hearings (Box 9-3)
    - Historic Riverway (Box 9-3)
    - I.B.M. (Box 9-3)
    - I.B.M. Contracts (Box 9-3)
    - Inland Wetlands (Box 9-3)
    - In-Service Training Courses (Box 9-3)
    - Insurance (Box 9-3)
    - Internal Revenue Service (Box 9-3)
    - Intergovernmental Personnel Act (Box 9-3)
    - Inventory System (Box 9-3)
    - Job Analysis Questionnaire (Box 9-3)
    - Job Specs (Box 9-3)
    - Joint Funding Simplification Act of, 1974 (Box 9-3)
    - Kaman (Box 9-6)
    - Kreines, Ted. (Box 9-6)
    - Laboratory Fees (Box 9-6)
    - Land Acquisition (Box 9-6)
    - Land Acquisition-Open Space, before 1976 (Box 9-6)
    - Land Acquisition-Policies (Box 9-6)
    - Land Acquisition-Program Review Committee Report (Box 9-6)
    - Land Acquisition-Proposed Manual (Box 9-6)
    - Land Acquisition-Spec. Act Authorizations (Box 9-6)
    - Latham, January ice (Box 9-6)
    - Legal (Box 9-6)
    - Legis. Management Committee (Box 9-6)
    - Legis. Forms (Box 9-6)
    - Legislative Research (Box 9-6)
    - Levitsky & Berney (Box 9-6)
    - Library (Departmental) (Box 9-6)
    - Library (Box 9-6)
    - Licensing & Revenue, before 1975 (Box 9-6)
    - Lumber Mill (Box 9-6)
    - Lunatic Fringe (Box 9-6)
    - Management Analysis (Box 9-6)
    - Management Study (Box 9-6)
    - Manpower Ind. Waste Facilities (Box 9-6)
    - Mansfield-Coventry Regional Sewer System (Box 9-6)
    - Mashamoquet Brook State Park (Box 9-6)
    - Massachusetts Div. of Fisheries & Game (Box 9-6)
    - Metric Coord. Comm (Box 9-6)
    - Mohawk Lease (Box 9-6)
    - Monthly Analysis of Appropriation Requirements (Box 9-6)
    - Multigraphics Division (Box 9-6)
    - Municipal Assistance Program (Box 9-6)
    - Municipal Grants Programs (Box 9-6)
    - Municipal Correspondence (Box 9-6)
    - Municipal Wastewater Control (Box 9-6)
    - National Marine Fisheries Serv. (Box 9-6)
    - Nasorlo (Box 9-6)
    - New England Regional Commission (Box 9-6)
    - Newsletter-Dept. (Box 9-6)
    - Newspaper Clippings (Box 9-6)
    - N.Y. State Dept. of E.P. (Box 9-6)
    - Northeast Utilities Variance Request (Box 9-6)
    - Noise Control (Box 9-6)
    - NRSTEN Communications Network (Box 9-6)
    - Nursery (Box 9-6)
    - OPM-Planning & Energy Policy (Box 9-6)
    - OPM-Tax Division (Box 9-6)
    - Office of State Planning-Correspondence (Box 9-6)
    - Office Services (Box 9-6)
    - Oil Refinery (Box 9-6)
    - OMB Circulars (Box 9-6)
    - Open Spaces-Status of Grants to Towns (Box 9-6)
    - Operating Budget Request-Fiscal, 1973 (Box 9-6)
    - Operations & Enforcement (Box 9-6)
    - Organization Charts Units (Box 9-6)
    - Organization Chart B of H (Box 9-6)
    - Organizations (National & International) (Box 9-1)
    - Organization charts (Box 9-1)
    - Parking Tag Objection (Box 9-1)
    - Personnel-Central Office (Box 9-1)
    - Personnel-Conservation and Preservation (Box 9-1)
    - Personnel-Environmental Quality (Box 9-1)
    - Personnel-Policy, Planning, and Research (Box 9-1)
    - Personnel-Resumes (Box 9-1)
    - Personal Services Projections (Box 9-1)
    - Personnel-Retirements (Box 9-1)
    - Personnel Summaries (Box 9-1)
    - Pesticide Control (Box 9-1)
    - Plan of Conservation & Development (Box 9-1)
    - Policy and Procedures Manual (Box 9-1)
    - Portland Maintenance Depot (Box 9-1)
    - Postage (Box 9-1)
    - Press Releases, 1975 (Box 9-1)
    - Press Releases, 1974 January (Box 9-1)
    - President’s proposed budget, 1973 (Box 9-1)
    - Probate Court (Box 9-1)
    - Procedures (Box 9-1)
    - Program Associates (Box 9-1)
    - Program Review Committee, 1975 (Box 9-1)
    - Program Review Committee, 1974 (Box 9-1)
    - Properties Review Board (Box 9-1)
    - Prospect Beach (Box 9-1)
    - Public Works Department (Box 9-1)
    - Public Works Employment Act (Box 9-1)
    - Purchasing & Equipment (Box 9-1)
    - Purchase Requests (Box 9-1)
    - Taylor, Robert B. (Box 9-8)
    - Title 3-WR Planning Act (Water Resources) (Box 9-8)
    - Title 10 (Box 9-8)
    - Title 20 (Box 9-8)
    - Transmittal Forms (Box 9-8)
    - Trumbull Town Clerk (Box 9-8)
    - Dana (Box 9-8)
    - Mt. Bushnell-Burnham (Box 9-8)
    - Werner (Box 9-8)
    - Bingham (Box 9-8)
    - Tundermann, David (Box 9-8)
    - U.S. Coast Guard Agreement (Box 9-8)
    - U.S. Dept. of Agriculture (Box 9-8)
    - U.S. Forestry Service (Box 9-8)
    - U.S. Dept of Commerce (Box 9-8)
    - U.S. Dept of Interior (Box 9-8)
    - U.S. Geological Survey (Box 9-8)
    - University of Hartford (Box 9-8)
    - University of New York (Box 9-8)
    - U.S. G.S.-Water Resources (Box 9-8)
    - Upgradings (Box 9-8)
    - Vacation Schedule, 1975 (Box 9-8)
    - Washington Trips (Box 9-8)
    - Water Bank Program (Box 9-8)
    - Water Compliance (Box 9-8)
    - Water Pollution-Monthly Financial Statements (Box 9-8)
    - Water Pollution-Source Material (Box 9-8)
    - Water Resources (Box 9-8)
    - Water Resources Council (Box 9-8)
    - Water Resources-Source Material (Box 9-8)
    - Welfare Dept. (Box 9-8)
    - W. Rock Ridge St. Park (Box 9-8)
    - Wetlands (Box 9-8)
    - Wildlife Unit (Box 9-8)
    - WIN Program (Box 9-8)
    - Wolcott Race Track Decision (Box 9-8)
    - Adkins, Ralph-Personal (Box 9-8)
    - Workmen’s Compensation Division (Box 9-8)
- Series 8. Hearings, 1973-1984; 1988-024
  - Part 1, 1973
    - Connecticut River Crossing Hearings, January 1973 (Box 7-1)
      - Hearings. Volumes 1 to 15 (Box 7-1)
    - Delso Brothers Hearing (Norton River) transcripts, 1973 (Box 12-1)
    - Department of Environmental Protection vs. Alwin Construction transcripts, 1973 (Box 11-1)
    - Solvents Recovery, 1974 (Box 3-1)
      - Air Pollution (Box 3-1)
      - D’Addario (Box 3-1)
      - D’Addario Construction Hearing (Box 3-1)
      - Solvents (Box 3-1)
      - Solvents Recovery (Box 3-1)
      - Record - City of Milford (Box 3-1)
      - Transcript of Hearing - Solvents Recovery Service of New England Book 1 (Box 3-1)
      - Transcript - Book 2 (Box 3-1)
      - Transcript - Book 3 (Box 3-1)
      - Transcript - Book 4 (Box 3-1)
      - Transcript - Book 5 (Box 3-1)
      - York Research Report (Box 3-1)
      - SRS Burning Lob - 1972 Exhibit SS (Box 3-2)
      - SRS Burning Log - 1973 Exhibit TT (Box 3-2)
      - VV to XX (Box 3-2)
      - Solvents Recovery Exhibits A-N (Box 3-2)
      - Solvents Recovery Exhibits O (Box 3-2)
      - Solvents Recovery Exhibits P (Box 3-2)
      - Solvents Recovery Service of N.E. Hearing Files (Box 3-2)
      - Solvents Recovery Service of N.E. Transcript Book 1 (Box 3-2)
      - Transcript - Book 2 (Box 3-2)
      - Transcript - Book 3 (Box 3-2)
      - Transcript - Book 4 (Box 3-2)
      - Transcript - Book 5 (Box 3-2)
  - Part II, 1975 (Box 8-1)
    - Wolcott Race Track Hearings, 1975 September 22 (Box 8-1)
      - Transcripts from Hearing Re: Old Rock Road Corporation (Box 8-1)
      - Application for Wolcott Race Track (Box 8-1)
      - Transcripts from Hearing Re: Old Rock Road Corporation (Box 8-2)
      - Application for Wolcott Race Track (Box 8-2)
  - Part III, 1978-1979
    - Public Hearings, 1978-1979
      - Arcangelo, Charles V. (Box 10-1)
      - Avalone, Lawrence J. (Box 10-1)
      - B & B Associates, 1979 May 10 (Box 10-1)
      - Beard, Dan, Inc. (Box 10-1)
      - Bombeck, Hans and Cheryl (Box 10-1)
      - Bottle Bill hearing, 1979 July 6 (Box 10-1)
      - Bruno, Alfredo, 1979 September 28 (Box 10-1)
      - Bushka, Edward, 1979 November 5 (Box 10-1)
      - Cavanaugh, Caroll (Box 10-1)
      - Chaney, William R. (Box 10-1)
      - Commodore Marina - Oral arguments (Box 10-1)
      - Commodore Marino, 1979 October 17 (Box 10-1)
      - Connecticut River disposal sites (Box 10-1)
      - Connecticut River - Water Resources Unit, 1979 May 25 (Box 10-1)
      - Cuisubarts - Oral arguments (Box 10-1)
      - Daly, John J. III (Box 10-1)
      - DiCambio - Oral arguments (Box 10-1)
      - DiNardo (Box 10-1)
      - Department of Transportation - Fijol (Box 10-1)
      - Department of Transportation - #74 Torrington, 1979 March 13 (Box 10-1)
      - Department of Transportation - Routes 8 and 15 (Box 10-1)
      - East Haven Sewer Commission (Box 10-1)
      - Gesner, Melvin, 1979 September (Box 10-1)
      - Gillette's Castle, 1979 April 30 (Box 10-1)
      - Graves Marina, 2 folders (Box 10-1)
      - Groton, Town of (Box 10-1)
      - Groton, Town of, 1979 September 11 (Box 10-1)
      - Gustaferri, Anthony - Show cause, 1979 September 18 (Box 10-1)
      - H & B Associates (Box 10-1)
      - Higgins, Richard - IW 608 (Box 10-1)
      - Hunt (Newton L.) & Punzelt (Philip M.) (Box 10-1)
      - Hunt & Punzelt - O/A, 1979 October 28 (Box 10-1)
      - Indiantown Association (Box 10-1)
      - Iowa Terminal & Warehouse Inc. (Box 10-1)
      - Juranie, Dwight, 1979 April 24 (Box 10-1)
      - Kennan, Hugh, 1979 August 3, 17 (Box 10-1)
      - Larson Pond Dam (New Lakeview Convalescent) (Box 10-1)
      - New Haven Harbor dredge (Box 10-1)
      - New London redevelopment (Box 10-1)
      - Noank Shipyard, 3 folders (Box 10-1)
      - Norwalk, City of [oral arguments] (Box 4-1)
      - Owen, Nicholas (Box 4-1)
      - Palmer, Mr. & Mrs. (Box 4-1)
      - Parrilla, Joseph and Kenneth, 1979 September 12 (Box 4-1)
      - Pistey, Charles, 1979 June 15 (Box 4-1)
      - Pistey, Charles (Reconvened) (Box 4-1)
      - Pistey, Charles O.A., 1979 September 13 (Box 4-1)
      - Potter, Jackson (Box 4-1)
      - Press, Carl, 1979 July 12 (Box 4-1)
      - Ragged Rock Marina, 1979 August 29 (Box 4-1)
      - Russell, Warren and Marilyn (Box 4-1)
      - St. Margaret’s McTernah, 1978 September 18 (Box 4-1)
      - Salmon River (Box 4-1)
      - Saunders, and Lavoie (Box 4-1)
      - Shell beach Arguments, 1979 August 28 (Box 4-1)
      - Steamboat Wharf, 1979 May 9 (Box 4-1)
      - Stradmore Development (Box 4-1)
      - T.C. Construction Co. IW #593 (Box 4-1)
      - T&M Builders/Nector, Inc., 1979 October 29 (Box 4-1)
      - Tarius, Leo, 1979 May 8 (Box 4-1)
      - Time Associates (Box 4-1)
      - Trefz, Christian J., 1979 April 9 (Box 4-1)
      - Unimax Switch Corporation, 1979 April 11 (Box 4-1)
      - Village Savare Property (Box 4-1)
      - Wagner, Robert, 1979 November (Box 4-1)
      - Welsh Pond Dam (Box 4-1)
      - Wies Frederick, M.D., 1979 September 26 (Box 4-1)
      - York Haven Marina (Box 4-1)
      - Youngman (Box 4-1)
      - Ziegler, Paul (Box 4-1)
  - Part IV, 1979-1984 (Box 6-1)
    - Hearings, 1979-1984 (Box 6-1)
      - Acme Chemical, 1980 July 7 (Box 6-1)
      - AGC Inc., 1981 September 21 (Box 6-1)
      - AGC Inc. Oral Argument (Box 6-1)
      - ASL Associates (Box 6-1)
      - Bodnur Ernest (Box 6-1)
      - Bass Plating (Box 6-1)
      - Bodnur, E., 1980 January 28 (Box 6-1)
      - Bombaci and Bartlett, 1983 January 15 (Box 6-1)
      - Bostitch, 1984 May 12 (Box 6-1)
      - Bradley, Kenneth, 1979 August 30 (Box 6-1)
      - Bradley, J. Kenneth, 1979 October 31 (Box 6-1)
      - Bradley, J. Kenneth, 1979 November 29 (Box 6-1)
      - Bradley, Kenneth J. O/A (Box 6-1)
      - Bristol Myers Company (Box 6-1)
      - Buckland Hearing, 1982 February 24 (Box 6-1)
      - Bushka, 1981 April 15 (Box 6-1)
      - Bushka O.A., 1981 June 16 (Box 6-1)
      - Canton, Town of (Box 6-1)
      - CBL Inc., 1982 July 12 (Box 6-1)
      - Central Coast West/Quinnipiac River Basin (Box 6-1)
      - Commodore Marina, 1980 April (Box 6-1)
      - Conarc, 1982 July 19 (Box 6-1)
      - Cromwell/Middletown (Box 6-1)
      - Crowley, Stephen, 1984 September 10 (Box 6-1)
      - CRRA, 1984 October 19 (Box 6-1)
      - Crystal Mall O.A (Box 6-1)
      - Crystal Mall Oral Argument, 1980 August 25 (Box 6-1)
      - Crystal Mall, 1980 January (Box 6-1)
      - D’Addario, 1982 February 16 (Box 6-1)
      - D’Addario, 1982 January 10 (Box 6-1)
      - Dept. of Mental Retardation, 1984 April 30 (Box 6-1)
      - Dept. of Mental Retardation, 1984 (Box 6-1)
      - DOT I-86 (Box 6-1)
      - DOT Manchester, 1980 November 19 (Box 6-1)
      - DOT Manchester Remand Hearing, 1981 September 2 (Box 6-1)
      - Dritenbas, 1981 October 29 (Box 6-1)
      - Dritenbas, 1981 March 19 (Box 6-1)
      - K-F Brick, 1982 July 2 (Box 6-2)
      - Kirla (Box 6-2)
      - Kirla (Box 6-2)
      - Kirla (Box 6-2)
      - Lanafill Associ. Oral Arguments, 1983 July 26 (Box 6-2)
      - Laurel Park 3rd Session (Box 6-2)
      - Laurel Park O/A, 1982 June 24 (Box 6-2)
      - Laurel Park O/A, 1984 July 20 (Box 6-2)
      - Lebanon (Box 6-2)
      - Levine & Millstein (Box 6-2)
      - Levine & Millstein Hearing, 1984 August 2 (Box 6-2)
      - McHugh Hearing, 1982 January 19 (Box 6-2)
      - Middletown, 1983 October (Box 6-2)
      - Midway Mall, 1983 (Box 6-2)
      - Montville Landfill (Box 6-2)
      - Montville Landfill, 1983 November 29 (Box 6-2)
      - Montville, 1984 March 26 (Box 6-2)
      - Montville, 1984 June 19 (Box 6-2)
      - Montville, 1984 June 21 (Box 6-2)
      - Murtha, 1981 December 18 (Box 6-2)
      - Segretario, Stephen, 1980 October 3 (Box 6-3)
      - Segretario, S. O/A (Box 6-3)
      - Sockriter, Jay, 1982 September 30 (Box 6-3)
      - Solvents Recovery (Box 6-3)
      - Solid Waste Disposal Inc., 1984 July 5 (Box 6-3)
      - Stratford Land and Improvement Company O/A, 1980 July (Box 6-3)
      - Sulfur Utilities, 1981 February 24 (Box 6-3)
      - Terminex, 1983 February 25 (Box 6-3)
      - Terminex, 1983 March 2 (Box 6-3)
      - Teminex, 1983 April 25 (Box 6-3)
      - Thames River Basin, 1983 June 2 (Box 6-3)
      - Union Manufacturing, 1982 July 6 (Box 6-3)
      - Union Manufacturing, 13-Sep (Box 6-3)
      - Warehouse Associates, 1980 February 13 (Box 6-3)
      - Warehouse Associates, 1981 March 1 (Box 6-3)
      - Warehouse Associates, 1981 March 2 (Box 6-3)
      - Westport, 1980 May 16 (Box 6-3)
      - Westport Recreation Dept., 1984 February 1 (Box 6-3)
      - Windham Sand & Stone, 1982 December (Box 6-3)
      - Yaworski Hearing, 1984 December 19 (Box 6-3)
      - Yaworski Hearing, 1984 February 8 (Box 6-3)
      - Yaworski Hearing, 1984 February 9 (Box 6-3)
      - Yaworski Hearing, 1984 April 2 (Box 6-3)
      - Yaworski Hearing, 1984 April 23 (Box 6-3)
      - Yaworski Hearing, 1984 May 9 (Box 6-3)
      - Yaworski Hearing, 1984 July 3 (Box 6-3)
      - Yoney, 1979 November 14 (Box 6-3)
      - Yoney Realty Corporation, 1980 January 25 (Box 6-3)
      - Zeigler Hearing, 1983 January 13 (Box 6-3)
      - Radio Information (Box 6-4)
      - Recycling (Box 6-4)
      - Refuse Disposal System (Box 6-4)
      - Regulations Committee (Box 6-4)
      - Reid and Riege (Box 6-4)
      - Relocation (Box 6-4)
      - Resource Conservation & Development Projects (Box 6-4)
      - Resource Recovery Authority (Box 6-4)
      - Retirement Commission (Box 6-4)
      - Revenue Report (Monthly) (Box 6-4)
      - Rocky Neck (Box 6-4)
      - Senator Lowell P. Weicker (Box 6-4)
      - Service Ratings (Box 6-4)
      - Shell Fisheries (Box 6-4)
      - Silver Sands St. Park (Box 6-4)
      - Slater, Karen M. (Box 6-4)
      - Snake River (Box 6-4)
      - Snowmobiles (Box 6-4)
      - Soil Conservation-Correspondence (Box 6-4)
      - Solid Waste, 1973-74 (Box 6-4)
      - Solid Waste, 1972 (Box 6-4)
      - Solid Waste through, 1971 (Box 6-4)
      - Solid Waste NERC Proposals (Box 6-4)
      - Solid Waste Refuse Collection Demonstration Proposal (Box 6-4)
      - Speeches (Box 6-4)
      - Staff Memos (Box 6-4)
      - State Liaison Officer (Box 6-4)
      - State Library (Box 6-4)
      - State Planning (Box 6-4)
      - State Police (Box 6-4)
      - Status Reports-Air (Box 6-4)
      - Status Reports-Appropriation Rearmts. (B-66) (Box 6-4)
      - Status Reports-Boating Fund (Box 6-4)
      - Status Reports-Bond Fund (Box 6-4)
      - Status Reports-Financial (Box 6-4)
      - Status Reports-Overall Picture (Box 6-4)
      - Status Reports-Personal Services (Box 6-4)
      - Status Reports-Solid Waste (Box 6-4)
      - Status Reports-Trust Funds (Box 6-4)
      - Status Reports-Water (Box 6-4)
      - Stevens, Gerald F. (Box 6-4)
      - Stewart, Renee B. (Box 6-4)
      - Summer Employees, 1976 (Box 6-4)
      - Sundry Operating (Box 6-4)
      - Telephone Credit Cards (Box 6-4)
      - East Haven Industrial Park (Box 6-5)
      - Durham Poultry Farms, Inc., 1982 February 4 (Box 6-5)
      - East Haddam (Box 6-5)
      - Electrolux (Box 6-5)
      - Elm City Cheese, 1984 September 21 (Box 6-5)
      - Elm City Cheese, 1984 December 19 (Box 6-5)
      - Essex, 1981 October 28 (Box 6-5)
      - EWR, 1983 September 22 (Box 6-5)
      - Environmental Waste Removal (Box 6-5)
      - Fidelity (Box 6-5)
      - Fidelity (Reconvened) (Box 6-5)
      - FIP Corporation, 1982 September 15 (Box 6-5)
      - Forman, 1983 June 15 (Box 6-5)
      - Gilbert Madelyn, 1981 March 5 (Box 6-5)
      - Ideal Forging, 1983 May 25 (Box 6-5)
      - Ideal Forging O/A, 1984 February 15 (Box 6-5)
      - I-84, 1980 May (Box 6-5)
      - I-84 Part 2 (Box 6-5)
      - I-84 Part 3, 1981 June 13 (Box 6-5)
      - IT&T Hearing, 1984 July 26 (Box 6-5)
      - IT&T Oral Argument, 1984 July 6 (Box 6-5)
      - J&M Incorporated (Box 6-5)
      - Jajer, Maurice, 1980 August 6 (Box 6-5)
      - Jenson, Robert & Ruth, 1981 October 16 (Box 6-5)
      - Johnson, Herbert, 1982 February 10 (Box 6-5)
      - Juliano, Frank and Jerry (Box 6-5)
      - Juliano, Frank and Jerry, 1981 June 26 (Box 6-5)
      - Karlin, Toby, 1979 (Box 6-5)
      - Karlin, Toby, 1980 October 24 (Box 6-5)
      - Keeney Cove, 1980 January 31 (Box 6-5)
      - K-F Brick, 1982 August 31 (Box 6-5)
      - Napier, 1982 April 26 (Box 6-6)
      - Napier, 1982 April 26 (Box 6-6)
      - Napier Company (Box 6-6)
      - Napier Company Oral Agreements (Box 6-6)
      - Napier, 1982 April 30 (Box 6-6)
      - Nash Family, Inc., 1979 May 30 (Box 6-6)
      - New Milford Home Builders, Inc., 1980 July 16 (Box 6-6)
      - New Milford Home Builders, Inc., 1980 December 2 (Box 6-6)
      - O’Brien Hearing, 1981 February 9 (Box 6-6)
      - O’Brien Oral Argument, 1981 April 13 (Box 6-6)
      - Old Lyme, 1980 August 18 (Box 6-6)
      - Old Saybrook Oral Argument, 1982 June 9 (Box 6-6)
      - Oxford Fells (Box 6-6)
      - Peck, Arnold, 1980 January 10 (Box 6-6)
      - Pfizer (Part 1), 1981 August 10 (Box 6-6)
      - Pfizer (Part 2) (Box 6-6)
      - Phelps Dodge, 1980 November 23 (Box 6-6)
      - Phelps Dodge, 1980 November 18 (Box 6-6)
      - Portland, Cromwell, 1980 March 11 (Box 6-6)
      - Pratt &Whitney, 1982 July 14 (Box 6-6)
      - Royce (Box 6-6)
      - Royce (Box 6-6)
      - Pratt & Whitney, 1983 April 26 (Box 6-6)
      - Russo, Joseph, 1980 October 31 (Box 6-6)
      - Russo, Joseph, 1980 December 5 (Box 6-6)
      - Russo, Joseph, 1980 December 4 (Box 6-6)
      - Russo, 1980 December 3 (Box 6-6)
      - Russo, 1981 March 18 (Box 6-6)
      - Russo, 1980 October 23 (Box 6-6)
      - Sasco Creek, 1980 July 15 (Box 6-6)
      - Safeway Products, 1983 February 25 (Box 6-6)
      - Santanelli, Lewis, 1984 April 25 (Box 6-6)
  - Carbon Copies, 1979 (Box 14-1)
    - Hearings, 1979 (Box 14-1)
      - Achenback, 1977 October 13 (Box 14-1)
      - Addison Bog (Box 14-1)
      - Addison Bog (reconvened) (Box 14-1)
      - Allen, Howard K., 1978 March 8 (Box 14-1)
      - Allen, Howard K., 1978 April 18 (Box 14-1)
      - Allen, Howard K. Oral Argument (Box 14-1)
      - Archangelo, Charles V., 1978 April 11 (Box 14-1)
      - Banca, Attilio, Florence and Peter (Box 14-1)
      - Banning (Box 14-1)
      - Banning-Oral Arguments (Box 14-1)
      - Battelle- Wm. F. Clapp Labs (Box 14-1)
      - WC Beth- Mor 1 (Box 14-1)
      - WC Beth- Mor 2 (Box 14-1)
      - WC Beth- Mor- Oral Arguments (Box 14-1)
      - Better Formed Metals (WC), 1978 June (Box 14-1)
      - Boccanfuso (Box 14-1)
      - Bogardous (Box 14-1)
      - Boy Scouts of America (Quinnipiac Council) (Box 14-1)
      - Bradley, J. Kenneth (Box 14-1)
      - Bradley, J. K. Oral Arguments (Box 14-1)
      - Bride Brook Relocation (Box 14-1)
      - Bride Brook Oral Argument, 1978 June 15 (Box 14-1)
      - Bustin, Kenneth, 1978 March 28 (Box 14-1)
      - Bustin, Kenneth O/A, 1978 September 21 (Box 14-1)
      - Caruso Bros. Oral Arguments (Box 14-1)
      - Casey Corp. Oral Arguments (Box 14-1)
      - Castle Rock (Box 14-1)
      - Cedar Island Marina (Box 14-1)
      - Cedar Island Marina Oral Argument, 1978 July 25 (Box 14-1)
      - Chaplin- Wetlands Delin. (Box 14-1)
      - Chenrock, Joseph (Milford Harbor) (Box 14-1)
      - Civil Penalties- Appendix E (Box 14-1)
      - Clinton, Town of (Box 14-1)
      - Clinton, Town of, 1978 January 24 (Box 14-1)
      - Commodore Marina, 1978 April 6 (Box 14-1)
      - Commodore Marina, 1978 May 31 (Box 14-1)
      - Conn. Paper Bd.- Montville (Box 14-1)
      - Conn. Paper Bd. – Montville, 1978 May 31 (Box 14-1)
      - Cromwell Meadows, 1978 October 16 (Box 14-1)
      - Crowley, James A., 1978 April 25 (Box 14-1)
      - Cuisinarts, Inc. (Box 14-1)
      - DiCambio- Dredge, September 14 (Box 14-2)
      - DiCambio- Dredge, 1977 September 23 (Box 14-2)
      - DiCambio- Dredge, 1977 November 18 (Box 14-2)
      - DiCambio- Dredge, 1977 December 7 (Box 14-2)
      - DiCambio- Dredge, 1978 February 14 (Box 14-2)
      - DiCambio- Dredge, 1978 February 28 (Box 14-2)
      - DiCambio- Dredge, 1977 December 8 (Box 14-2)
      - DiCambio- Waterline, 1977 September 13 (Box 14-2)
      - DiCambio- Waterline, 1977 September 22 (Box 14-2)
      - DiCambio- Waterline, 1977 November 9 (Box 14-2)
      - DiCambio- Waterline 1 (Box 14-2)
      - DiCambio- Waterline (Box 14-2)
      - Derby, CT of (Box 14-2)
      - Dinardo, Ralph (Box 14-2)
      - Dinardo, 1977 November (Box 14-2)
      - Dinardo, Ralph Oral Argument, 1978 April 3 (Box 14-2)
      - Dept. of Transportation project #161-100 Wilton (Box 14-2)
      - Dutch Wharf (Box 14-2)
      - East Haven (Box 14-2)
      - East Haven (Shell Beach), 1978 January 11 (Box 14-2)
      - East Haven Economic Development Comm. (Box 14-2)
      - East Haven Economic Development - Oral Arguments (Box 14-2)
      - East Lyme, 1977 December 14 (Box 14-2)
      - East Village Association (Box 14-2)
      - East Village Association, 1977 September 7 (Box 14-2)
      - Environmental Waste Removal - w.c. (Box 14-2)
      - ESM Associates (Box 14-2)
      - Faggella, Vincent (Box 14-2)
      - Faggella (re-opened) (Box 14-2)
      - Fairfield, Town of (Pine Creek), 1977 July 11 (Box 14-2)
      - Fairfield, (Pine Creek), 1977 September 7 (Box 14-2)
      - Field, Solomon (Box 14-2)
      - Forest Grove (Box 14-2)
      - Forest Grove (reconvened) (Box 14-2)
      - Forsell, Louis, 1978 May (Box 14-2)
      - GMS Construction (Box 14-2)
      - Glastonbury Dyeing + Finishing Co. (Oral Arguments) (Box 14-2)
      - Guilford Yacht Club (Oral Arguments) (Box 14-2)
      - Guilford- East Creek (Box 14-2)
      - Guille, Peter (Box 14-2)